[
	{
		"id": 1,
		"area": "Transportation",
		"category": "Private",
		"type": "negative",
		"question": "How many miles a week do you drive or Uber?",
		"answers": ["0", "< 20", "20 - 60", "60 - 100", "100+"]
	},
	{
		"id": 2,
		"area": "Transportation",
		"category": "Public",
		"type": "negative",
		"question": "How many miles do you travel each week by public transport?",
		"answers": ["0", "< 20", "20 - 60", "60 - 100", "100+"]
	},
	{
		"id": 3,
		"area": "Transportation",
		"category": "Public",
		"type": "negative",
		"question": "How many hours do you fly by plane each year?",
		"answers": ["0", "< 10", "10 - 30", "30 - 60", "60+"]
	},
	{
		"id": 4,
		"area": "Transportation",
		"category": "Non-Emittable",
		"type": "positive",
		"question": "How many miles a week do you get around by walking, biking, etc..?",
		"answers": ["0", "< 20", "20 - 60", "60 - 100", "100+"]
	},
	{
		"id": 5,
		"area": "Energy",
		"category": "Electrical",
		"type": "negative",
		"question": "How many hours per day do you watch tv?",
		"answers": ["0", "1 - 6", "7 - 12", "13 - 19", "20+"]
	},
	{
		"id": 6,
		"area": "Energy",
		"category": "Electrical",
		"type": "negative",
		"question": "How many hours a day are your lightbulbs in use?",
		"answers": ["0", "1 - 6", "7 - 12", "13 - 19", "20+"]
	},
	{
		"id": 7,
		"area": "Energy",
		"category": "Water",
		"type": "negative",
		"question": "How many times a week do you use a dishwasher?",
		"answers": ["0", "1 - 2", "3 - 4", "5 - 6", "7+"]
	},
	{
		"id": 8,
		"area": "Energy",
		"category": "Water",
		"type": "negative",
		"question": "How many times a week do you take baths or showers?",
		"answers": ["0", "1 - 5", "6 - 10", "11 - 14", "15+"]
	},
	{
		"id": 9,
		"area": "Energy",
		"category": "Water",
		"type": "negative",
		"question": "How many times a week do you use a washer and dryer?",
		"answers": ["0", "1 - 2", "3 - 4", "5 - 6", "7+"]
	},
	{
		"id": 10,
		"area": "Energy",
		"category": "Renewable",
		"type": "positive",
		"question": "What percentage of your appliances are energy efficient or energy saving?",
		"answers": ["0", "<25%", "25 - 50%", "50 - 75%", "75 - 100%"]
	},
	{
		"id": 11,
		"area": "Energy",
		"category": "Renewable",
		"type": "positive",
		"question": "What percentage of your appliances use renewable energy?",
		"answers": ["0", "<25%", "25 - 50%", "50 - 75%", "75 - 100%"]
	},
	{
		"id": 12,
		"area": "Food",
		"category": "Renewable",
		"type": "negative",
		"question": "How much meat do you eat each week?",
		"answers": ["Never", "Once in a while", "Some days", "Most days", "All the time"]
	},
	{
		"id": 13,
		"area": "Food",
		"category": "Renewable",
		"type": "positive",
		"question": "How much of your food is locally sourced?",
		"answers": ["None", "Some", "Half", "Most", "All"]
	},
	{
		"id": 14,
		"area": "Waste",
		"category": "Renewable",
		"type": "positive",
		"question": "How do you recycle plastic waste?",
		"answers": ["I throw it in the garbage", "I sometimes recycle", "I always recycle", "I reuse my items", "I never use plastic products"] //HuHHH
	},
	{
		"id": 15,
		"area": "Waste",
		"category": "Renewable",
		"type": "positive",
		"question": "Do you compost?",
		"answers": ["No", null, null, null,"Yes"]
	},
	{
		"id": 16,
		"area": "Waste",
		"category": "Renewable",
		"type": "positive",
		"question": "Do you use reusable grocery bags?",
		"answers": ["Never", null, "Sometimes", null, "Always"]
	}
]
